Chaya Hutchinson

(229)-513-9850 | hutchinsonchaya8@gmail.com | Perry GA

Professional Summary

Detail-oriented problem solver with 350+ training hours and experience in Web development. Interested in attaining a career that will allow me the opportunity to excel as a web developer as well as highlight my previous work experience and leadership abilities.

Skills

- W3Schools JavaScript Certification (in progress; expected date of completion 02/2023)
- Basic engineering
 Data Entry
 Leadership
- Basic programming
 Microsoft Word
 Active listening
- Critical thinking
 Communication
 JavaScript
- Microsoft Excel
 Problem Solving
 HTML
- Adaptable
 Customer Service
 CSS

Experience

Zaxby's, Byron GA - Cashier

December 2017- March 2019

- Operated the register on an as-needed basis
- Provided services necessary for customer satisfaction
- Cleaned work area before, during, and after shifts
- Maintained a professional relationship with teammates and customers alike

McDonald's, Perry GA - Kitchen Manager

July 2019 - October 2021

- Trained crew members
- Ensured food safety procedures
- Steadily providing food for customers
- Ensured the kitchen and equipment are clean

Bath and Body Works, Remote - Seasonal Customer Service Assoc.

November 2021 - January 2022

- Communicated with customers effectively to ensure satisfaction
- Provided sales in a fast-paced environment
- Determined the quickest ways to answer questions and offer assistance

•

Elevation Connect, Remote - Travel Support Representative

March 2022 - Current

- Connect with guests via phone or email
- Resolved guest issues with necessary de-escalation skills
- Sent maintenance tickets to the local teams
- Assisted with modifying reservations and processing payments
- Provided feedback from calls and made important notes

Education

Generation USA Jr. Web Developer Program, Remote GA Certificate of Bootcamp completion

August 2022 - Current

Peach County High School, Fort Valley GA High School Diploma

August 2017-May 2018

Lee County High School, Lee County GA

December 2015- July 2017